A new day!
Good morning, Snezhnograd!
...This is all the way from Natlan!
Ohh!
We gotta get our hands on those gems...
...Mm-hmm!
*hum*...
Natlanese gems...
The ball
The gangs...
These are troubled times...
Here, keep the change
Huh?
Ah...
Lady Vesna!
Vesna...? Ugh!
...Huh?
Such a lively ball...
How could I miss it?
I hear you're after the gems?
Well, I'm sorry...
But so am I
Ugh!
For the Tsaritsa!
Attack!
Finish the job! We'll be rich! Charge...!
In your dreams, you're going to jail!
Surround them!
Thank you so much
I can't believe those brutes
Warranted the Druzhna...
Them?
Oh, they didn't
...What?
...Fabricating import logs is a crime
And using forbidden alchemy to forge gemstones?
An aggravating factor
So, I hope you had a good night...
But the afterparty's gonna be in prison